<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kevin Mattheus Moerman</title>
    <description>Research Scientist, MIT Media Lab</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 15:30:57 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 15:30:57 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.6.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Introducing the ORCA initiative</title>
        <description>Introducing the Open Research Code Advocates (ORCA)
The Open Research Code Advocates (ORCA) initiative (launched after the 2017 NUMFOCUS Summit &amp;amp; Sustainability Workshop, October 10th–11th, 2017) is a website where open source enthusiasts join as “advocates” to help promote open source. Advocates also help develop resources about open source software allowing the website to grow into the go-to resource to help convince coworkers about the importance of open source.

The ORCA project is still very much a work-in-progress. More details to follow…



  

The Open Research Code Advocates (ORCA) initiative


</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/blog/2017/10/15/Introducing-the-ORCA-initiative/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/blog/2017/10/15/Introducing-the-ORCA-initiative/</guid>
        
        <category>post</category>
        
        
        <category>Blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pre-print Automated and Data-driven Computational Design of Patient-Specific Biomechanical Interfaces</title>
        <description>Automated and Data-driven Computational Design of Patient-Specific Biomechanical Interfaces
A new pre-print has been released about a novel design framework I have developed for biomechanical interfaces such as transtibial prosthetic sockets (Moerman et al. preprint).



   

Left: Schematic flow of socket design framework. Right: Animation showing morphing of a prosthetic socket design around a virtual limb


</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/blog/2016/09/19/Socket_preprint/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/blog/2016/09/19/Socket_preprint/</guid>
        
        <category>post</category>
        
        
        <category>Blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
